<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DreamSpace</string>
    <string name="text_label_3">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_label_1">Home</string>
    <string name="text_label_2">Journal</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="greeting">Good Afternoon</string>
    <string name="home_ready_text">Get ready for sleep:</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="add_dream">+ Add dream</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="version">Version 0.0.1</string>
    <string name="dreamspace">DreamSpace</string>
    <string name="settings_about">About</string>
    <string name="settings_notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id" translatable="false">681977230656-kjui3j960tkoif1g96r9dngbt152ajak.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="lang">language</string>
    <string name="lang_settings">Language settings</string>
    <string name="ru">Russian</string>
    <string name="en">English</string>
    <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
    <string name="hint_body">Write your dream here...</string>
    <string name="save_dream">Save dream</string>
    <string name="type_1">Dream</string>
    <string name="type_2">Nightmare</string>
    <string name="user_name">Dreamy</string>
    <string name="me">Designer and Developer:\n Kirill Rykhlov\n Contact with me: rihlov.kirill@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="dream_type">Type of dream:</string>
    <string name="dream_rate">Dream score:</string>
    <string name="evening">Good Evening</string>
    <string name="night">Good Night</string>
    <string name="morning">Good Morning</string>
    <string name="auth_fail">Authentication failed.</string>
    <string name="auth_succes">Authentication successful.</string>
    <string name="fill_fields_err">Fill in all the fields!</string>
    <string name="rate_err">Rate your sleep!</string>
    <string name="type_err">Choose the type of sleep!</string>
    <string name="add_dream_succes">Dream has been successfully added!</string>
    <string name="add_dream_error">Error adding sleep</string>
    <string name="google_signin_fail">Google sign in failed</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter a name</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="body2">How to Remember More Dreams\n\nIf you came across this article, you probably already know how important it is to keep a dream journal. If you don’t, and you want to learn more about the benefits of dream journaling, you can read our dedicated article:Why you should remember your dreams\n\nHow to remember your dreams better\n\nSetting and intention\n\nLike a lot of other practices, you need to be well prepared before you start. First, make sure you set a real interest and an intention to explore your dreams. Make sure your sleep environment is prime for a good night\'s rest. Try to have a relaxing evening routine. With good settings and a real intention, it will be quicker and easier to build your dream work practice. \n\nKeep a dream journal\n\nKeeping a dream journal is a proven way to build dream recall. The best way to prevent your dreams from fading away is to write them down immediately when you wake up when they are fresh in your mind. After only a few minutes, most of your dreams will be gone if you don’t make an effort to remember them. It can also happen that you wake up from a dream in the middle of the night. In that case, if you’re motivated enough, it’s important that you write it down. You may be tempted to think that you’ll remember this dream when you wake up, and you’ll write it in the morning. But it’s likely that when morning comes, you’ll have forgotten this dream entirely.\n\nRead this article on How to keep a good dream journal\n\nGet enough sleep\n\nSleep hygiene is important for getting good rest and vivid dreams. Many factors contribute to a good night’s sleep. Check out our other article on Tips For Better Sleep\n\nMorning hours are prime\n\nIn the morning, you should avoid abrupt awakenings: instead of jumping out of bed to switch off your alarm, ideally, you should take a moment to concentrate on what you were dreaming of before you woke up. Then gently get up and promptly write it down in your journal.\n\nIt doesn’t have to be perfect\n\nWhen keeping a dream journal, especially when you start, there will be mornings when you don’t remember anything, or you wake up with just a blurred memory, a vague emotion. It doesn’t matter what it is, write it down anyway. You can simply check a box where you say you didn’t remember anything, or write down some keywords to describe whatever feeling or memory comes to your mind. This way, you keep building the habit of writing in your journal every morning. And even if it’s not much, it’s always better than nothing when you’ll come back to it later.\n\nGo back at what you wrote\n\nThe practice of dream journaling is not just about writing down your dreams. It’s also about reading them again. Every now and then, you should go back and read your previous entries in your journal. If you feel comfortable with it, you can even share your dreams with someone you trust. Saying them out loud or even just reading them again will help you train your dream memory. It may also unveil some other elements you forgot or reveal some insights to understand your dream. Doing this regularly will improve your dream recall, therefore it’s a very good thing to do when you start dream journaling, and you still don’t remember much from your dreams.\n\nFocus on the right things\n\nOf course, when you write down a dream, the story is important. But it’s far from being the only thing to write down. There are some key elements to record to have a better understanding of the dream. First of all, focus on your emotions. How did you feel in that dream? Was it bad or good? What emotions did you experience? There is often more than one emotion — the more you can identify, the better. Pay attention to the elements in the dream: characters, themes, actions, places, etc. What are they? How do you interact with them? Are they familiar or even recurrent in your dreams. Focusing on these elements and writing them down will help you to make the most accurate description of your dream.\n\nExtra tip\n\nIf you’re very motivated, here’s an extra tip to go further.\nOnce you wrote down your dream, you should look for the elements related to your previous day. To do so, you can write a brief summary of your day before going to sleep, and then see which elements came into your dreams. This way it will be easier to understand why some things appear in your dream, and what elements you should focus on.</string>
    <string name="title2">How to Remember More Dreams</string>
    <string name="title1">Wht You Should Remember Your Dreams</string>id. A reason is that unlike the events from our daily l
    <string name="body1">Often, people will wake up in the morning thinking that they didn’t dream, but they dife we are used to remembering, dreams are usually unpredictable and illogical, which makes them quite hard to memorize. Also, most dreams are kept only in short-term memory, and this explains why, if we don’t make an effort to remember them, they will quickly disappear when we wake up. This is sad because, as you will read below, there are many benefits to remembering your dreams. But before diving into this, let’s first address a widespread belief: what if you think that you don’t dream at all?  Do we all dream the same?  Yes, we all dream every night. The truth is we all have several dreams each night, but we mostly remember the ones we had just before waking up. Most people report only one dream per night simply because they woke up once, in the morning. On the other hand, some people regularly remember several dreams per night, because they wake up more often during the night. So while we all dream, the ability to remember our dreams vary a lot between individuals. Of course, our ability to remember our dreams is linked to our memory, and some people have a better dream memory than others.   There are a lot more characteristics that are correlated with dream recall. For instance, women tend to remember their dreams better than men, and young people better than older people. People that are more creative, open to new experiences, and interested in their emotions are better too. Scientists also noticed that people living in urban environments had a greater dream memory, although this may be explained by the ambient noise-causing more night awakenings, which relates to remembering more.   The benefits of remembering our dreams  Remembering our dreams is the first step to getting all their benefits and exploring their huge potential. First of all, dreams can be an incredible source of ideas. Like the painter Salvador Dalí, whose paintings were often inspired by his dreams, or the scientist Dmitri Mendeleev who saw the periodic table of the elements in a dream. You probably have creative solutions and ideas to find in your dreams. In fact, studies found that people who remember their dreams tend to be more creative and have better problem-solving skills than others.   Consolidates memories  Dreams play an important role in the process of memory consolidation. Recollections from your week are incorporated into your dreams and remembering them strengthens those memories and improves your overall recall capacity. Our brains also delete uneccesary memories and send the important ones to long term memory storage.   Reveals dream patterns  Dream journaling over an extended period of time can reveal patterns, through recurrent dreams or the repeated appearance of important details in your waking life, and the more familiar your mind becomes with these patterns, the more awareness it might begin to have in wielding them while asleep. Repeated imagery, or dream symbols can be analyzed to better understand your subconscious and dream content.   Breaks creative blocks and solves problems  Dream journaling can also be a way to break a creative block. Dream researchers believe that the subconscious mind creates scenarios to solve particular problems or explore the curiosities of a day’s events, bringing all those things you may have seen or heard without much thought into the light. A possible explanation is that the bizarreness and unusual characteristics of dreams stimulate a different way of thinking.  Helps practice lucid dreaming  Last but not least, remembering your dreams is the first step to analyze and interpret their content, but also to control them —see our articles about lucid dreams. Keeping a dream journal not only helps build dream recall, but it also develops your ability to lucid dream. The more you write down your dreams, the easier it will get to remember them and the more awareness you will have overall within the dream. Helps us process emotions and prepare for the unexpected  Uncomfortable emotions that we avoid in our waking experience can seep into our nightly visions. Dreams may have a survival function when it comes to helping us prepare for situations we may not commonly encounter in our waking lives.Evolutionary theory suggests that nightmares may help us adapt to potential real-life situations. According to the “threat simulation theory,” dreams allow us to practice moving through stressful environments in order to help us prepare for fear-inducing circumstances in the waking world. That might explain why dreams are often accompanied by falling, running away from someone or something, or finding ourselves in embarrassing conundrums.  How to recall your dreams better  Dreams contain a lot of information about yourself, that you’ll only be able to exploit if you remember them. The most efficient way to start remembering your dreams is to keep a dream journal. The core idea is to write down everything that you remember about your dream immediately after you wake up. Do this not only in the morning but also in the middle of the night if it happens.  Consistent practice of meditation and mindfulness exercises is linked to a higher dream recall —among many other benefits. Then, science found out that some substances like vitamin B6 and anxiolytics may have an increasing effect on dream memories.   There may even come a point at which you remember more information than what you can write down in a reasonable amount of time! If you’re not sure where to start or what to write, we created the perfect dream journal app for you! With DreamSpace you can easily write down useful information about your dreams, which you can then use with the other features, such as statistics and analyses. We hope we’ve convinced you to start writing your dreams!</string>
</resources>